http://www.manta19.miwd.co.uk/page/privacy-policy

RegisterLogin WelcomeManta HistoryManta StatisticsManta FAQ'sManta 19 BrochureManta 16 BrochureAssembly GuideOther Manta 19sTrailer Sailer LinksSite NoticesLatestblogsforumold messageboardSearchhomehomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyWe are committed to safeguarding your privacy online.Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of this site.Information We Use1.   Why We Collect Information. We collect information only to validate your identity during login or when you need assistance from the site administrator.2.   How We Collect Information. Your information is collected from the details you fill in on the registration page.3.   Who Has Access To Your Information. ONLY your Username is visible to other users of this site but this does not have to be your real name. You may create your account using a pseudo Username and may change your Username at anytime at your discretion. All other personal information is only accessible to the site administrator. Your information will not be shared with any third party, unless we are obliged to do so to by an official legal authority.CookiesThe site uses cookies to control some functionality of the site. The cookies used are:MantaTrailerSailer is used store the Session ID. A session is needed for the website to manage events such as whether a user has or has not logged in.cookiesAccepted is set when you accept the cookies used by this site. It is used to suppress the 'This Site Uses Cookies' message for your current visit.fontChanger is used to store your font choices if you have changed your default font size. It is only created if you choose to save your font choice in a cookie.chatLeft and chatTop are used to store the screen position of the Live Chat window. These are only set if a logged user has used the website Live Chat feature and has moved the live chat window to a new position on their screenNo personal data is collected or stored in cookies used by this site.Security OnlineWhilst security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, whilst we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, you do so at your own risk.You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information.The information you publish in blog pages and the forum on this site, is visible to all visitors and users of this site. Take care not to publish any detailed personal information that may leave you vunerable to fraud and/or identity theft.Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. ContactPrivacy PolicyTerms and ConditionsSitemap TopHelpContactPrivacy PolicyTerms and ConditionsSitemapAdverts© MI Web Design  This Site Uses CookiesPlease read our Privacy Policy for full details.Accept
